Do you have any cigarettes?
I left it for you
Thanks, I miss my wife.
forage circle
Clear the scene
children go to ground
Please check external site
Sierra Kilo
No external site problems
Checking on children who came up from underground
Backpack man man on the move
Dad
Doyeonah
Dad!
dad!
Dad
Doyeon!
Doyeonah
no
But
Dad, why are you sleeping in my room?
Oh my dad
Did you get scolded by your mom again?
Oh my
no
Doyeon came to see me
I fell asleep
Dad
Does it hurt?
uh
It hurts
hungry
Because Doyeon is too heavy
Come on, let's get up.
I have to wake up and go to kindergarten
Huh? Come and wash up quickly
Yeah
this morning
Changni-dong, Giyun-si
At an ATM machine booth
There was an explosion
a foreign man
He died at the scene.
Police said this man was at a nearby convenience store.
After purchasing butane gas
Immediately after entering the ATM booth
A strong explosion occurs
the entire booth
They said it was damaged
In this accident
Two citizens passing by
I suffered minor injuries after being hit by debris.
The man who died recently
Enter the country with a short-term stay visa
A place on the outskirts of Giyun City...
Ugh
I'm glad you stopped
Go take out the trash
What have you been doing?
I said I took a walk around the neighborhood.
Did you think it would suddenly explode?
As soon as I moved in
What's going on?
Call the company people
Have a housewarming
Housewarming?
The Sullivan ruling comes out
If this house is worth shit...
Anyway, until Doyeon goes to college.
I won't be fired from the company
You don't have to go
This is a housewarming event.
I'm trying to persuade you to take a good look.
Oh, that means a lot, huh?
I want you again
Call our employees
I thought you were going to cross-examine me.
Now, shall we go out and make some money?
Sounds like butane gas.
I also touched the news
Even soldiers on the scene
Are you a deserter?
silencer for foreigners
And if it's MK2, what about terrorism?
in korea?
Or the 8th US Army?
in a few hours
Put all that away
Find out the cause of the explosion
You even brought a new ATM machine?
Wow, long live Korea!
Huh?
A country that handles things so quickly
Where are you in the world?
Isn't it?
yes, no
There are a lot of strange things in my eyes.
Well, it's strangely fast.
If that explodes at night
Do you remember what color it was?
What, fire color?
No, not even in flames
There are many colors
So, it's red or something.
Yellow or something...
I fell to the floor in shock
I was hanging my head down
What color is it!
I have to go to work
Ah
Unless that's the original maker unit
don't know the difference
But because I didn’t serve in the military.
Of course you don’t know!
Sounds like butane gas.
Bodhisattva Choi, good morning
I'm fine thank you, and you?
Fine thank you
Report posted yesterday
It ended well without a companion, for some reason
The face...
Did you fight?
Did you get squeezed by Jesu?
Hey, didn't you see the news?
Butane gas explosion at Giyun intersection
i was there
It's like the mark of a survivor
Did Choi Bodhisattva news come out?
Oh, celebrity
Hey, but that neighborhood
Well, the days go by
Car exploded, butane gas exploded
It's not like I'm talking nonsense
It's me
You released this kid?
Which family are you from?
The guy who hit Sullivan's daughter with his car.
He is the son of the National Assembly Speaker.
Just in case
As expected, the expectations are not wrong.
It's amazing, it's amazing
Was there a Supreme Court ruling?
Uh, just now
Sounds like laws and principles
I'm doing it, these are
ruined
About this ruling
Please tell me something
Civil litigation in the future
Are you planning?
Unless it's a lawsuit
such as withdrawal of investment
Are you considering economic retaliation?
Everyone
Is money everything in life in Korea?
Let's go
James Sullivan
They said they would build an Asian hub.
A site on the outskirts of Giyun City
You made a huge purchase.
That's right
Because of that, the government
Asia's best IT special tourist zone
I announced that I was making it.
But
This ruling today
Oh, what should I do with this?
The guy who killed my daughter
In Korea, they just release it
Do you want to invest?
If you're like me
I don't do it
But here are some stupid ants
What are these ants going to do?
So
To be honest
If Sullivan falls out
Isn’t this the end of special zones? uh?
I went in believing only what the government said.
Aren’t only the ants losing money?
There is no answer...
Giyun intersection
Did you find the car involved in the accident?
They say it's in Bongbong's junk car.
I'm going to go see it now.
Not our customers
Did you get the other person’s car wanted?
I will definitely find him too.
Team leader, don’t go anywhere.
Just wait here
Oh, Ace
Kinda cool?
- it's awesome?
- Uh
- Is it cool?
- then!
My wife is having a housewarming party
I want to set a date
Oh, good
Post a notice in the group chat room
Yesssul
Yes?
Why don't you have a car?
Why why?
It doesn't exist because it doesn't exist.
No, looking at the documents
This was the only record of scrapped cars.
Then you should have two.
Why one?
Oh, give it to me quickly.
Ah, well
I don't know the car that hit me
Only the one who got hit came in.
I really don't understand
Because Wrecker saw the scene
You don't know
Oh, please tell me!
Oh, I'm busy.
Why the fuck are you coming here?
I don't know!
If you go in front of there and hit the left room,
There's a car with all the windows broken, huh?
What happened and how
It's so shit
Go check that out
I didn't drive
I'm trying to save people
gray and smoky
Jump into that fire pit...
Gray smoke...
It's dangerous!
Both bombs?
Oh my, Mr.
Dog training at night
I'm not telling you to do it
Oh my, my knees, Mr.
Where did you go?
Where did you go? Mr.
Gun?
There was definitely a gunshot sound.
That's right
Ha, this raccoon guy
Did you take off the hour hand?
Oh, you little raccoon
Why can't I see any faces?
huh? Can't you see it here?
Does this make sense?
The butane gas I bought at the convenience store exploded.
People died and buildings were damaged.
The bigger problem is
residents
I'm shaking with anxiety.
Accordingly, I contacted the butane gas manufacturer.
A strong protest...
What is that
Are you talking about a dog eating grass?
Thank you
No, someone died
What's the bigger problem? uh?
They say we're shaking
Because the gas explodes
It's so mouth-watering
Oh, I'm excited, I'm excited
Who is that person?
- Hello, hello
- Oh, yeah.
National Assembly member Naeun-jae Yoh
Room 307 Didn’t you go to work?
I went out to work
Police officer Park of the district unit?
I came to see you and you said you were here
Police officer Park?
Me, me, me, me, me
That's Police Officer Park.
What are you doing now?
I don't know
Well, I guess I came here to sell light.
No, butane gas is the problem.
I have to go to that company and ask about it.
I don't know why I come here and dig for mines
Still a member of the National Assembly
I'm trying to do something for you.
Just be kind to me
That's it
What are you trying to do for me? uh?
What you really need
Without even doing it
Hey there!
hey!
yes
No, well, ‘I’m full after eating.’
Don't say such obvious things
with the taxes we paid
Please install some CCTV, okay?
They say Korea is a CCTV heaven.
Even if you wash your eyes and look for this neighborhood,
There are few
That's right, it's not even at the intersection.
Who are you...
Oh, me?
58th graduate of Giyun Girls’ High School
I'm the president of the Changni-dong women's association.
When campaigning before
Come to our store and get it
We just shook hands and did that.
Not yet
I did that part
I was just about to tell you.
Due to this accident
Now, build a control system and
Even the risk that there might be
Intelligent CCTV that notifies you in advance
We will fully introduce it
Isn't that the latest one? huh?
It's good, right? oh
And what happened recently in Giyun City?
Unsavory things happen
Yes, responsibility will be revealed until the end.
Legal responsibility!
Let me ask you
Rep.
You have to go for your next appointment.
Are you going?
That one, that one, it's not blocked
I see you drinking alcohol
Who wrote that, huh?
Anyway, I'm good at memorizing things.
unlucky year
in high school
He looked so proud and scared
Even though I'm just president of the women's association,
What...
Minister Kim has been contacted.
yes
Because I took the medicine
tell me
Butane gas
Does that make sense?
Ah, it’s strange to anyone who sees it!
Where did you get the press release from?
Minister
You have to tell me whether it's poop or intestines.
I also respond accordingly.
You stupid military brat
Hey, let's go
It's so noisy that I'm dying.
IC
Is it poop or soybean paste?
I'm dying of confusion too.
Wow, I'm annoyed, Mr.
'There is
'No justice in Korea'
President James Sullivan
leaving the court
What you left is a hot topic.
Today the Supreme Court
President James Sullivan's daughter
The late Miss Charlotte Sullivan
To Mr. Kwon, the defendant in the traffic accident case.
found not guilty
"European Champions Final
“Elite VIP Package Ticket”
Okay, reservation complete
uh
Teacher!
Teacher, why don’t you read my DMs?
I didn't know you had a DM
Is it teacher I?
MBTI?
yes
One, two, three, four
Five, six, seven, eight!
yap!
Block the cross!
Special martial arts!
♪ I love you baby ♪
♪ I don’t know what’s next ♪
Everyone take a seat!
Now, the voice of the cool manager.
Can you hear me?
Your voice is small! Hey!
It was good
You guys are at the playground
I'm playing alone
When a strange man or woman comes up to me
'Hey'
‘I am your father’
‘I’ll buy you something delicious.
'Do you want to come with me?'
What should I do if this happens?
Well done
But my voice is small
I can't hear you
Now, in times like this
Blow this whistle, do it
Hey!
That's enough, that's enough, that's enough!
stop!
Uh, ah, good job.
Okay, then later
You guys are going home alone.
A strange woman came
‘Hey, what should I do?
'Your mother is very sick'
‘I’ll take you to the hospital.’
What should I do if this happens?
Is my mom sick?
Where is the hospital?
No
Oh, right!
Now, everyone, applaud Doyeon!
Well done, Doyeon
You have to blow the whistle like this
Okay?
Wow, what a surprise.
Are you here, father?
Hey, Doyeon is the best, Doyeon
Dad
When you meet a bad adult
I'll scold you with a whistle.
Yeah yeah
Until your ears bleed
Just scold me, just
Yeah
Ah, to our kindergarten
Olivia, the art teacher, is here.
-Olivia?
- Yes
Shala Shala Shala Shala
Just say it in English like this
Oh, that shala shala shala
Native teacher?
Yeah
Oh my, that's right
By the way, today mom
Because I'm not in a good mood
Don't bother asking me to show you the video.
Chi
I'll buy you a sticker instead
secret from mom
Yes, secret!
- secret
- Shalla Shalla Shalla
- Shalla Shalla
Oh my, thank you for your hard work
Uh, loyalty
Hey, Police Officer Park
Would you like to have a cup of coffee with me?
Should I be arrested if I hit him?
Hey, then hit him and arrest him.
Oh no
I'm popular today, really.
Oh, good luck, yeah
- Good work
- Yes, trouble, yes.
No, who came again?
What happened when the ATM exploded, member of the National Assembly?
I'm calling a press conference.
Who is Giyun intersection?
Ask about the traffic accident
Crossroads traffic accident? who?
I heard it's SIU.
Hey, are you from the government?
No, insurance inspector.
Well, with my brother in the early morning
There was a guy I was with.
Ah, that guy's job
Is that it, S line?
SIU...
- Yes, SIU, yes.
- Yes
Brother, why did you come?
uh?
No, well, I
Man dead at ATM machine
I'm a bit curious about who it is
Oh, that
The case was taken to the police station.
I don't know
Looking at the news, it seemed like the case was closed.
um
I see.
Hey
Are you just for me
I want to tell you separately
Well, there is no such thing, right?
I want to tell you the way out
Uh, okay, uh, good job
Yes, good luck
Oh, I enjoyed it.
Please take care, brother.
Oh my, Byeong-gu.
Were there any guests?
Man, I was waiting for you.
Oh my, I'm sorry.
Have you waited long?
- No
- No?
Now
- Let's go in.
- Yes
Wherever you go, you go
Either write it down
Doyeon, I'm choosing stickers.
Dad, I'll go to the hardware store.
Yeah
Wait a minute
boss
Now
Giyun intersection traffic accident
You were there at the scene, right?
'president'?
So?
About accident vehicles
Do you remember anything?
I need to do you a favor.
I'm completely out of my mind
Well, brothers
What are you trying to remember?
Except it exploded
You say you don’t remember anything.
Um, have we met already?
Even though I didn't go to the military
It's pretty quick.
Are you an SUV driver?
Being carried away or something
Like a license plate or something.
Is there anything that comes to mind?
well
Trying to save people
When I'm crazy, it explodes
License plate and all.
Didn't you see anything?
Oh, I see.
Did you see the accident from the beginning?
It was there from the beginning
So what, do you look from the middle?
I also have a question
If they answer
I think something comes to mind too.
Okay, what's your question?
Didn't you really hear a gunshot yesterday?
When I chased that guy
That's too much
If you don't want to tell me
Just say no
What gun, what gun, huh?
I'll do the sticker calculation over there.
Why has this continued to rust?
It doesn't work, this is so...
What are you trying to do with this?
Ah...
How much is this?
20,000 won, it’s written there.
What, living or not living?
Do you provide lifetime A/S for this as well?
Are you a sheepish person?
in which country
Do you provide after service for Doraiba?
Then it's too expensive, I won't buy it
Hey, in Kiyun City
It also smoothes out nasolabial folds.
I came here because I heard there was a laundry master.
You were the bank manager?
If you look closely at our room 307,
Not only does it make a good impression
I think I have a good personality too
Oh, did I get caught again?
Oh, I can't hide this.
You can't fool my eyes
This is just something
You can take it slow
Because it's not urgent
Uh, leave it there.
yes
Hey
Well, I have a lot of work to do.
I guess you're late from work?
Oh, this?
This deacon up there
The son of that house
I got a job this time
I left it to you to wear on your first day at work.
i forgot
Fortress here
There were a lot of messy things going on.
Oh my, room 307 too
As soon as I arrived, oh my
Well...
Oh, that's right
In this sermon’s words,
A man who got into an accident early in the morning
in front of
They say it’s like Hyeonju Artville’s bachelor?
Are you not a foreigner?
draw, so
I guess it stood out more
It's old there, the building is
There are a lot of empty houses
Oh, really?
Good luck
What are you doing there?
uh? with that face
Oh, I almost had a heart attack, Mr.
That's exactly what caught me
Why, what else?
What are you trying to frame me for this time?
The criminal must be at the scene
It always appears again.
The culprit? who?
Oh, uncle?
Don't lift the hour hand
We're talking about that now.
What did you come looking for?
Our Choi Kang?
I came for health, health, huh?
Walking is also good for preventing dementia.
Because it also prevents aging
oh
Why?
Well, this town
Can’t you even go for a walk?
Do I have to pay a fine for that too?
You came to look for shell casings, right?
What shell casing?
I came back after serving in the military.
I know the sound of a gun with a silencer well.
That's here
When I was hanging out with that guy yesterday
Did you hear a gunshot?
either that way or that way
They say someone shot it
It's strange that you're not surprised, huh?
A guy who didn't even go to the military
Maybe
Are your ears a little bad?
Talk too much
Say...
What?
They say it's too harsh
and
If you shot
Everyone in the neighborhood must have woken up.
I'm exempt from military service
Are you afraid they don’t even know the sound of a gunshot?
Get out of the way, do some exercise.
It's a gun with a silencer
Did you talk about it?
Are you going to pretend not to know until the end?
Yes, I do.
Let's see where and how far we can go.
Okay, look.
Because I'm going to go all the way to the other side
Bosch to your heart's content
and
Mr. Hardware Store, be careful out at night.
In that dark place
If you suddenly put that face in my face
That's violence
Do you know?
What about my face!
What's wrong!
Brother
There's still a lot of patrol time left.
Why has it been so long already?
Hey
Come and lock the door
Why do you lock the door?
I guess it's important
Doyeon’s father?
yes
Because there are more than one or two strange things
What is that
Because I have special motor skills
You must be good at running.
And on that camera
It's probably a coincidence that it didn't come out
How do you avoid all that, bro?
Yeah, like you said
Let's just say it was a coincidence once
But I changed the camera position
You changed everything?
I didn't get caught this time either.
This is 100%, man
It knows where the camera is and moves.
Plus, it's weird whenever guns are mentioned.
I did that on purpose
It made the sound of reloading.
Then it turned like lightning
I heard you tried to kill me
Wow
Even man
Where did you get this?
I thought it was a real gun
This is a BB gun
Material, weight, everything is the same as the real thing
Look, you who served in the military are fooled too.
But
The person who never even served in the military
Don't even blink
Well, maybe you're not interested, bro.
I'm just saying
I said no, this bastard is really
This is also me in the field
I came for you, man.
what?
Wow, are these really bullet casings?
So I concluded
I guess the strongest
Looks like a spy
Spy?
Yeah
So
Do-yeon’s father is a spy.
The man who died in the explosion
Is he a black agent from the National Intelligence Service?
It could be the other way around, bro.
Oh, be quiet.
Talk to me, tsk
Hey, the ATM machine exploded
Cleaned it up in an hour
Butane gas is said to be the cause of the explosion.
announced on the morning news
This is all a cover-up.
Butane gas doesn't explode like that.
It seems to me
- It's a bomb.
- Bomb?
yes
Hey, just like you said
Let's say the man is a spy.
Then you would have kept quiet from the media?
It was featured in the headlines and there was an uproar.
- Brother
- Uh
Do foreigners work at the National Intelligence Service?
Hey, there are Asians in the CIA too.
In the global era
We have to localize it so we don’t get caught.
Well, in Korea
Nowadays, many foreigners are naturalizing
yes
But brother
Doyeon's father
Being a spy is a bit...
Hey, man, mr.
I'm HID, HID
Just believe me if I do, nigga
Follow me
Oh, that's right
A man who got into an accident early in the morning
in front of
They say it’s like Hyeonju Artville’s bachelor?
It's old there, the building is
There are a lot of empty houses
Brother
I don't think this is real
Oh, who steals?
Let's just check
Uh, here it is.
- Brother
-Why?
Hey, is this really the house?
You have so many questions
There are a lot of things I want to eat
Chunbae hyung
Taught me, nigga
Follow me
Oh, I don't think it's real.
cat sounds
Do you think you can hear it?
Hey
Should I just take a peek through the window?
Wait a minute
- Brother
- Huh?
why?
uh?
How did you open it?
Like this
I just opened it
Hey, Korea
Even if it's safe, it's like this
Do you leave without locking the door?
IC
Why, why?
No shoes, it feels like no one's there
Why are you scared when no one is there?
You were surprised, Mr.
- come out
-Why?
Are you coming in?
They said there was no one
Hey, what is this?
icy, icy
They said there was no one
They don't wear shoes
Meow
- You go to the temple.
- Why?
No time, man
yes
Ah, what is this?
So this smell...
Huh?
What is this?
Brothers!
There's nothing wrong here!
Byeongnam hyung!
Brother Sunam!
No, Brother Suil
Let's get out of here!
You have to get out, bro!
Brother, hurry up
Wait a minute, man.
It looks like there's someone inside.
Wait a minute
That doll smells like a bomb
The smell of a bomb...
What are you guys?
Who sent it?
Uh, honey
Uh, I'm going in a circle
The neighborhood is bigger than I thought
big
Oh no
I got some stray cats, uh, uh
Uh, sleep first.
Uh, I'll be right there, uh
What is it?
Why is that human coming out there?
Do-yeon’s father?
Sir, I got it right.
This bastard, this thing
Hey, Mr.
be quiet
- I'm sorry.
- What is that?
- yes?
I just brought it out because it was there, bro.
Shhh
Wait a minute
Talk to me
I do it
What is there to talk about?
If you do something stupid, report it right away.
Doyeon's father, by any chance
Are you a spy?
Ah, indeed
Someday, there will be no separate recycling
They treated me like a fool
What, now a spy? Mr. Lee
I saw it all, don't talk shit
That one is from room 203.
It's all captured here
So, did you take pictures of the one who ran away?
Let's take a look
Don't make a fuss
It's not a modified work.
Oh, really
That guy earlier
Looks like a spy
Traffic accident, explosion, and fire incident information
It's all collected by insurance companies.
Why?
Do I have to get compensation after an accident?
That's right
Among them, the SIU Insurance Investigation Team
The inside story of the incident
This is a department that looks deeply into
Don't talk nonsense
Why did you enter room 203?
Talk quickly
Listen to what the laundromat owner says
I went looking for evidence, evidence.
What evidence?
That man
evidence of being a spy
For example, a pistol with a silencer
Ha, look at this
You knew everything but pretended not to know?
This insidious man, this
Then that is the key evidence of espionage.
Well, the bounty.
Should I share it with you?
I don't plan on doing that, huh?
Because I don’t have one either? Mr.
What is this?
Ah, this happened unexpectedly
I brought it out
I am from the communications service.
Shall we open it?
What should I open?
I need to report it right away
Hey, do what you want
Don't talk nonsense
Did you enter room 203?
Tell me quickly why you went in
Ha, look at this?
Yonghee, look at this
Doyeon's father
No, no, no, no
If I don't get this, I'll be in big trouble.
Oh, I'm going to be in big trouble.
If you don't get this
Everyone dies
Ah, why did I get it so late!
What are you doing when you’re not coming in?
Uh, honey
After exercising now
It’s a convenience store in front of my house.
What time is it now?
Come in quickly
When I come, I bring some white milk.
yes
Spy or whatever
Buy some white milk and go home
I buy it
Report it
Yes, yes, I understand.
Brother, what should I do with this?
Should I report it?
Shall I open it?
I think I can open it
Oh, it must be dangerous, right? You have to report it, right?
Ah, I want to open it, but
I'm going crazy, really.
- Is it Gollum?
- yes?
Is it Gollum? Why are you confused?
Do what you want, man.
Mr.
Brother
You have to take this, this.
No, but I think you can open it?
It’s dangerous, so you should report it, right?
Oh, what are you doing, huh?
Let's open it, bro.
Once me?
- uh?
- Please calculate this.
Uh, hey, this is
I have to eat it by next week.
yes
Ah, but well, kids eat it quickly.
Hey, wait a minute.
Hey, this
It came out for an event.
Take this and feed it to me.
This is
You can leave it for a long time and feed it.
Oh, it's really okay...
Oh my
How can this kid be so gentle?
Oh my, I'm not even crying.
thank you
Go
Ah, cute
- Hello
- It's salty, it's salty
Yes?
Oh, I just left
baby mom husband
Because of the traffic accident at that intersection...
Come and only buy discounted items.
I bought it
The child is young and won't be able to work.
Wow, where
Are you going to visit the hospital again?
No, I'm going to the junkyard today.
Bongbong junkyard
Are you Bongbong?
my neighborhood
Was it a person?
I said it earlier
Huh?
ah! Wait, wait, wait, wait
We should drink together
I am a police box
I was at the scene of the accident that day
I even met all the witnesses.
No one knows where that car is.
Is the driver even alive or dead?
Well, how many people were on board?
Because no one knows
Even the Wrecker kids said that.
The wreckers around here
We all know each other
That Wrecker is a face I've never seen before.
Ah, I went after receiving a report.
I hit the ball one day
They just said shit
Well, maybe
Have you talked about it?
no
Well, we each set off.
I think I saw you briefly on the street on the way here.
accident and driving a car
They said they were going towards Hanbalsan Mountain.
What's there?
What's in the mountains?
There will be tigers and lions
Ah, inside there
There is a logistics center
Oh, oh, oh, what is it? That...
Is it Novus?
Why, you know what?
Novus?
Maybe Novus Logistics Center?
Yeah, that, that, uh, Novus, uh
Novus Logistics Center loading and unloading
Doing it there?
It's just a warehouse there.
The car spread before
I went out once
There was no one
Are you sure you went there?
Yeah
Wow, thank you for your hard work
What's going on?
Ah, I am
It is said to be the best of Vertigo Insurance.
Uh, a few days ago
The car that was in a car accident
I said I came this way.
Are you in here by any chance?
Answers are limited
This is private property, so please leave.
Ah, then...
Then I'm sorry
Ah, I am now
I feel like my bladder is about to burst.
Hey, take a moment to go to the bathroom.
Can't I use it?
ah! I'm peeing now...
It's private property
Entry is not permitted without permission.
Then inside
I'll just turn the car around and head out.
Round, round, yes?
Back up there
You can leave
The car is leaving
Ah, yes
What are we doing here?
Hey, not pee.
I'd say it's half way out, Mr.
be careful
That's right
Today
The instructor will take you there.
See you tomorrow, special attack!
Special attack!
uh
- Thank you, thank you, go easy, uh.
- Yes, thank you for your work.
Huh?
Isn’t Doyeon riding?
My dad is coming to get me
Oh, really?
And the sticker the uncle gave me
I put it here
Wow, you put it on well, it’s pretty.
- Doyeon!
- Wow, it’s pretty.
Huh? It's dad
Dad!
Dad
Doyeon!
Doyeonah
Are you okay?
uh? Are you hurt?
Dad
Oh, it's okay because dad is here.
yes
Hey, are you okay?
Um, Mr...
I said I would report it.
I'm sorry
Just open it and see
I was going to report it right away.
This is there
Because it's not general security...
Ah, why doesn't this open...
Hey, but in it
I guess there really is something, huh?
Doing something crazy like that in broad daylight
If you see me doing it
There is evidence of a crime in here
But what about getting rid of it?
You can never open it?
uh...
There is a way
Yeah?
What should I do?
What do you ask, man?
Even if I can't eat it
Now I'm curious too
Let's see
Then the three of us
We're in the same boat.
uh
Okay!
here
My military classmate Kim Seon-won
These are brothers from our neighborhood.
Oh, nice to meet you.
- Yes, that's okay.
- Uh...
Hey, hey, look at this.
No, no, no.
Wait a minute
a few years ago
Active duty captain
Received Bitcoin from a North Korean agent
Confidential military information of our country
You know the case where you were caught trying to pass it up?
Anyway, I was trying to hack KJCCS at that time.
I used a USB hacking device.
Poison tab
Huh? So is that a poison tab?
I also only heard it in words
No, poison tabs are old.
This is
The Yongmu Dojo you have here.
Made with the director's idea
Business number Seventeen
It's easy to understand
Can you please say it in Korean?
Ah, indeed
Oh, yeah, I mean...
Business, business number 17
than that, po, poison tab
Upgrade...
So improved...
You know hacking, right?
bad thing
It's bad, isn't it?
So, in USB format
It's a hacking device.
On the satellite computer
I haven't tried it yet
If not, edit the source
instead
far from here
Please go very far and use it
Don't put my company in danger.
Hey, I'm like that too
There's camaraderie, nigga
give it
Hehe, don't do that.
Let me cool you down
That one, huh?
A
A person must have shame
I saved a laptop that fell into water.
Even what's in it
What if I ask you to take it out?
What did you save and what did you get out of it?
Then why are we here?
- Hurry up, brother.
- Turn this on.
There is such a thing
If you talk like shit
Let’s understand it clearly
Let's fix this
If it doesn't work out, I'll contact you.
You talk like shit
How do you understand?
Come on, brother.
Good luck
Yes, please come in
- That's it.
- It's open, uh, it's open.
Hey, hurry up
“Tracking signal detected”
"Location: Changni-dong, Giyun City"
Hey, but
Why is that screen like that?
Okay, then what?
I thought it was a PC room computer?
Okay, so do it quickly, do it quickly
So let’s take a look and see what’s there?
Look
What is this?
Does that look like Giyun intersection?
uh?
Hey, that's right
That's right, it was an accident, uh
Hey, hey, right, right, right, that...
Oh! Hey, hey, that time
Chunbae and I
Soo-il was here with his brother, huh?
ah!
Ah, I was so nervous.
I feel like my intestines are twisted
My stomach hurts, so I need to go to the bathroom...
Come back
- We have to do this again.
- What are you doing again?
- Let’s start this again from the beginning...
- Just turn it around!
Who sent it?
Camas? BIJ?
tell me
Hey, I mean
Traffic accident at Giyun intersection
The ATM machine exploded
Are you saying this was done by the same guy?
All files are in English.
The dead person was also a foreigner...
Brother
Is it an international mafia?
International mafia?
Hey, this is...
Did you get anything?
Oh my, I went to poop.
Fell in the toilet...
Blood, blood, blood, blood, blood
Ah
Earlier, the guy on the motorcycle chased me
Was there anything else other than the accident video?
Uh, well, we haven't seen it all yet.
Same, same, same, look together
“Attempting remote control”
Huh?
what is that noise
who
I accessed and connected remotely.
sorry
Hey, wait a minute
'work'
'difficult'
‘Making it’
'JDD'
‘Special Operations Unit’?
J.D.D.
Special operations forces?
Do you know me?
Ki Yunxi, man
What is causing terrorism?
At the village bus terminal
The bus exploded
Okay, let's go
In our Changni-dong
How can something like this happen one after another?
Who on earth does something like that?
One car came separately and
They were just cleaning up the accident scene.
Are you both moving?
Do you think someone touched this?
They say it is only used for special killing operations.
Better than we thought
He's a much scarier person.
They recognize me right away
Subtitle: Jang Se-ri